

### **PROFILE**

As an experienced professional, I strongly believe in leadership and collaboration. achieving success in guiding transformation initiatives while effectively managing partner and client relationships. Leveraging advanced data analysis, I develop highly effective strategies, showcasing proficiency in complex datasets. With a focus on results, I ensure timely project delivery, maintain high standards of quality and innovation, and improve the sales process to drive revenue growth. My strategic mindset drives digital transformation user experiences demonstrating my commitment to being a proven achiever in the field

**Portfolio** 

**LinkedIn Profile** 





Scan/Click

## CONTACTS



+39 333 2978 268



giorgiofloriddia.tr@gmail.com



Italy - Rimini Willing to relocate

# **APPLIED SKILLS**

- GOOGLE ADS;
- **GOOGLE ANALYTICS**
- FACEBOOK LEAD ADS;

- DATA ANALYSIS; SENTIMENT ANALYSIS; PROJECTS MANAGEMENT;
- ACHIEVING GOALS;
- TRANSLATIONS
- COMMUNICATIÓN SKILLS;
- **PERSUASIVE** COPYWRITING.

## **LANGUAGES**

 ITALIAN; ENGLISH;



PORTUGUESE. 🔎 🌘 🔘

# GIORGIO FLORIDDIA

Digital Sales Project Manager **Digital Marketing Strategist** Linguistic Mediator

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### **DIGITAL SALES PROJECT MANAGER**

IEG Italy Jan 2024 - present | Rilmini (Hybrid) Advisory

- · Conception and promotion of digital services linked to offline initiatives provided to exhibiting companies in the Food & Beverage industry at trade fairs. Actively collaborated with businesses to enhance their digital presence and optimize the exhibition experience
- Sales of the realised digital services

#### DIGITAL INNOVATION CONSULTANT

PwC Italy Feb 2022 - Jan 2024 | Milan (Hybrid) Advisory

- . Managing the relationships with partners and clients;
- Ensuring the assinging project respects the defined DeadLines;
- Sales of projects about: Data Analysis Digital Transformation Open Innovation
- Providing recurring reports about ongoing projects (Excel Power Point);
- · Translating documents for all involved parties (English- Spanish Italian).

## INTERNATIONAL COMMUNICATION STRATEGIST | HYBRID ROLE

Freelancer | Oct 2020 - Feb 2022 | London/Rome International business introduction consultancy -

- Managing the relationships with partners and clients;
- Ensuring all actions and procedures are accomplished by the team;
- · Leading Communication strategies to wolrdwide audiences;
- Achieving defined goals throough Digital Marketing strategies

## **COMMUNICATION CONSULTANT**

Nirtya | Jan 2020 - Oct 2020

Corporate Communication Consultancy - Marketing and communication

- · Designing and monitoring brand reputation and influence;
- Defining target audiences and related data driven communication strategies;
- · Supporting creative activities (cowryting and podcast productions);

## **CRM SPECIALIST**

Assist Digital| May 2019 - Jan 2020

Marketing and Communication Consultancy - IT advisory

- · Defining and launching CRM campaigns;
- SMS DEM Campaigns, guiding designers for LPs.
- Multingual copywriting: Spanish, English, Italian;

# **EDUCATION**

# POLYTECHNIC UNIVERSITY OF MILAN - GRADUATE SCHOOL OF MANAGEMENT **MASTER OF DIGITAL INNOVATION - OPEN INNOVATION**

Sept 2022 - Dec 2022

#### LUISS BUSINESS SCHOOL

MASTER OF MANAGEMENT & TECHNOLOGY - WITH MAJOR IN DIGITAL ECOSYSTEM THE MASTER COURSE IS DELIVERED IN ENGLISH BY MOTHER TONGUE PROFESSORS

Sept 2018 - 2019

- · Digital Marketing and Communication;
- Content Marketing & Copywriting;
- Social Media Strategies;
- · Digital Transformation Processes.

#### UNIVERSITY OF TURIN

#### **BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN LINGUISTICS MEDIATION**

Sept 2014 - 2018

Learning foreign languages as English, Spanish and Portuguese;

Studying Mediation techniques;

Studying Translation techniques;

Studying general languages properties;

Learning communicative properties.